export const Data = [
    {
        question: 'What is NFT?',
        answer: <small>A non-fungible token (NFT) is a non-interchangeable unit of data stored on a blockchain, a form of digital ledger, that can be sold and traded. Types of NFT data units may be associated with digital files such as photos, videos, and audio. Because each token is uniquely identifiable, NFTs differ from blockchain cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin. <br/><br/>At GiftseaNFT, we are excited about a brand-new type of digital good called a non-fungible token, or NFT. NFTs have exciting new properties: they are unique, provably scarce, tradeable, and usable across multiple applications. Just like physical goods, you can do whatever you want with them! You could throw them in the trash, gift them to a friend across the world, or go sell them on an open marketplace. But unlike physical goods, they are armed with all the programmability of digital goods.<br/><br/>A core part of our vision is that open protocols like Ethereum and interoperable standards like ERC-721 and ERC-1155 will enable vibrant new economies. We are building tools that allow consumers to trade their items freely, creators to launch new digital works, and developers to build rich, integrated marketplaces for their digital items.</small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How do i earn profits ?',
        answer: <small>Sign up and login. Select one of the available and in stock NFTs, input the quantity you want to buy  and click on buy now, an Ethereum wallet address will appear where you’ll make payment and drop the proof of transaction; hash code, the smart contract will automatically confirm the transaction and transfer the units of the NFT to the designated account. It can be gifted to another user or can be held as a form of investment.</small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How do i change my password?',
        answer: <small>Click on forgot password, confirm your phone number or email address, click on send code.
        A code is sent to the phone number or email Address which is used in resetting the password
        Password must contain at least 8 characters, one number, one capital letter, small letter, and special character.
        </small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How do i change my investment value?',
        answer: <small>In the dashboard, there will be a button for the following, GIFT NFT, BUY NFT, an investment portfolio board showing the daily increase in value of the NFTs held by the user. It will detail the value in dollars, etherium, and percentage of daily growth and total % increase from the original value. </small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How to make payment?',
        answer: <small>After selecting an NFT and adding it to your cart, click on the cart and confirm the NFT and the quantity to be paid for, click on BUY button, it will lead you to an Ethereum wallet address which you’ll transfer the Ethereum value of the NFT to from your crypto wallet. After payment, return back to your dashboard and click on I have paid, it’ll ask for a hash code to confirm the transaction after which the site automatically assign the units of NFTs to your account.</small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How to confirm payment?',
        answer: <small>After payment, return back to your dashboard and click on I have paid, it’ll ask for a hash code to confirm the transaction after which the site automatically assign the units of NFTs to your account.</small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How to gift someone a gift',
        answer: <small>In your dashboard, click on GIFT NFT, you can either choose from the NFT cards you hold in your account or select from the listed and available options, you’ll be asked to input the person’s username and email address, then pay for the NFT or deduct from your holdings, once the transaction is confirmed, the NFT is automatically transferred to the user who then starts to receive the return on investment (ROI) immediately. Gifting NFTs is free of charge. </small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How to convert NFT to cash',
        answer: <small>NFTs can be converted to cash prematurely or once it reaches 6months.  If it is cashed out before the maturity date, the user will lose 30% of the original value, while it adds 50% value every six months a user hold on the assets. A user can decide to leave the NFT for years so as to accumulate as much as possible. For withdrwal, click on the NFT from your dashboard, you can decide to lock in the art for 1 year period or on cash out button, the value is calculated and you’ll be asked to provide an etherium wallet where you’ll receive the value of the transaction.</small>
    },
    {
        question: 'The safe lock button',
        answer: <small>An investor can decide to lock in his investment for a period of 1 year and earn 60% every six months instead of the normal 50% so that at the end of the year he has 120% ROI while the ordinary investor gets 50% per 6 months and 100% increase everywhere. </small>
    },
    {
        question: 'How to use the investment calculator',
        answer: <small>The investment calculator aids you to calculate the future value of any investment you want to make in the site. It helps you see the value in 6 months’ time, 1 year, 2 years, 3 years, 5 years, 10 years. It also helps you calculate the value in safe lock mode, the value if you decide to cash out before time.</small>
    }
    
]